LINKS

in LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/i
n/christos-kapsalis-lin/

GitHub:

https://github.com/ckapsalis2710

ABOUT ME

Full-stack software developer for almost 10 years in numerous software projects. Back-end development in Java, Lua and PHP. Front-end development in Javascript. Eager to learn new languages, technologies and undertake interesting projects. Accountable, working on schedule and comfortable working as a team member.

SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT/ REACT/ JQUERY/ HTML/ CSS/ BOOTSTRAP

JAVA/ LUA/ PHP/ C/ SQL/ BASH SCRIPTING

NODEJS/ EXPRESSJS

KUBERNETES/ DOCKERS

XML/JSON/AJAX/SVI

GIT/SVN

ROBOT/JENKINS

REGULAR EXPRESSIONS

VS CODE/ ECLIPSE (+SPRING FRAMEWORK)/ PHPSTORM/ CODECHARGE STUDIO

SQL CLIENTS (PGADMIN4, DBEAVER, DB VISUALIZER, DBBROWSER FOR SQLITE, NAVICAT)

DEVELOPER TOOLS /
POSTMAN/WIRESHARK

BALSAMIC (MOCK-UPS)

BROWSERS' WEB

AGILE

CMS

WINDOWS AND LINUX OS

LANGUAGES

GREEK

ENGLISH

ITALIAN

HOBBIES

HIKING/ CLIMBING/ SKI-SNOWBOARD/ TAEKWONDO/ SWIMMING

CHRISTOS KAPSALIS

FIII I -STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



+306947934771

xrikapsalis@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nov 2022 - Aug 2024 Sabbatical

NOKIA

Athens Dec 2021 - Oct 2022

Senior Technical Specialist

- **Back-end development** of Altiplano Controller, an open software GUI platform that served as an API to connect other Nokia's software units.
- Software development of a feature in Java, tested on JUnit, loaded on a Docker container, deployed on Kubernetes platform. Most of the work applied to arrange PODs configuration and their software interaction, under Kubernetes.
- Experience in Intent development logic, Microservices, Cloud based solutions, DevOps operations, Kibana search engine, Postman request engine.

NOKIA Athens

Sep 2016 - Dec 2021

Software Engineer

- Full-stack development of WebCT, a software that provided a GUI to administer X-Haul microwave products.
- Back-end development of WebCT in Lua and DB handling with Lua-Sqlite3. As well, development in Java with JUnit testing of ASLM, an app that produces licenses for all X-Haul products.
- Front-end development in Javascript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS, and Bootstrap framework.
- Involved with the full circle of a feature's production.
 Creation and reviewing of features' code, software architectural designs, Low Level Design, mock-ups,
 CuDo documents. Developing at least one feature per release while following a biannual release schedule.
- Peer reviewing of Code, Use Cases, Test Strategy and Test Cases.
- $\cdot\;$ Full stack Unit Testing and debugging code.

NOKIA

Athens Jun 2015 - Aug 2016

Software Engineer

- Full-stack software development of the FMANG application, managing Nokia's FlexiNG product. An app that offered mainly a GUI to monitor all kind of alarms, statistics and product health, like also managing all kind of product's configuration.
- Back-end development in Java and Java EE
 Development toolset: JSF/Primefaces, Spring,
 Hibernate, Maven, Tomcat, Jenkins, Junit.
- · Front-end development in **Javascript, HTML, CSS**.
- Change the whole product's GUI style after company's rebranding. Create some new features, debugging and peer reviewing of code. Milestone, to solve with the help of the team a crucial bug that maid the whole app to fail.

NOKIAAthens

Sep 2014 - May 2015

E&V Tester

- Responsible for **CI** Test suite of Nokia's LTE network gateway (FlexiNG) of around 400 Test Cases.
- Entity and Verification testing in **Robot** framework.
 Daily report on the CI state and fixing each TC that failed.
- Enhancing the CI by creating some new TCs.

CYBERTECHNICS INTERACTIVE COMMUNICATION LTD

Athens Dec 2012 - Jan 2014

Web Programmer/Developer

- Full-stack software development of Modus CMS.
- Back-end development in PHP. Front-end development in Javascript, HTML, CSS.
- Responsible for Back-end administration and development of Modus CMS.
- Updating and debugging CMS' code. Creating CMS' modules, components, droplets. Data handling through DB queries of production's applications, upon customers requests.
- Implementation of RAFM (Restricted Access File Manager) filesystem and integration of Ajaxplorer GUI into Modus CMS.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF PIRAEUS Piraeus

2011

University Degree in Digital Systems & Technology
 Education: Informatics

STOCKHOLM UNIVERSITY AND KTH JOINT DEPARTMENT

Stockholm 2009 Erasmus Exchange Student Program: Knowledge Management

COURSE

ZERO TO MASTERY

ACADEMYSep 2024 - Present

Fullstack Web Developer Career Path. Updating my knowledge on CSS, latest versions of Javascript, learning REACT, NodeJS with ExpressJS, PostgreSQL by building a full-stack app and using a Machine Learning API.